<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>My Stories</title>
  <icon>http://j.yud.co.za/stories/icon.png</icon>
  <subtitle>Josh Yudaken</subtitle>
  <link href="http://j.yud.co.za/stories/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://j.yud.co.za/stories/"/>
  <updated>2022-11-11T03:32:53.520Z</updated>
  <id>http://j.yud.co.za/stories/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Josh Yudaken</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Día de Muertos &#39;22</title>
    <link href="http://j.yud.co.za/stories/2022/11/09/Dia-de-Muertos-2022/"/>
    <id>http://j.yud.co.za/stories/2022/11/09/Dia-de-Muertos-2022/</id>
    <published>2022-11-09T05:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-11-11T03:32:53.520Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello over there! I’ve been struggling to find a way to share what I’m up to, that both feels easily accessible enough, but also private enough. I tried Instagram, but it feels too boastful, and with every post I had a renewed internal debate of why I was posting each image publicly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My single goal here is to share updates in a way that makes others feel connected (hello mom!), and keeps communication lines open. Instead of comments I’m going to encourage y’all to reach out to me on Signal&amp;#x2F;WhatsApp and have this act as a trigger for conversations there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;What-was-I-doing-in-Oaxaca&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#What-was-I-doing-in-Oaxaca&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;What was I doing in Oaxaca?&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;What was I doing in Oaxaca?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story dates back to October 2017, when for a lot of reasons I had decided I needed to take some time off work. It only lasted a couple months before I had to go back to San Francisco, but I spent six weeks in Oaxaca studying Spanish. I lived with a family there, ate meals in their house, and attending a school during the day. Luckily the timing also overlapped with October 31st through November 2nd. During those couple days, the city is lights up with a cultural explosion that, for me anyway, is one of the most special events on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon after that trip I decided at some point I needed to share the experience with friends. Around a year in advance I reserved a house in Oaxaca, and kicked planning into high gear about 3 months before. The house I found had eight bedrooms, and I was asking people to come for a little over a full week, so it was a challenge to fill the house. I was also being extremely picky on the invite list, trying to find a group that’d connect well, and also be willing to get a little weird. I was grateful for the friends that decided to trust me with their precious vacation time. In the end the last bedroom was taken two days before the trip was set to start.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>US West Coast</title>
    <link href="http://j.yud.co.za/stories/2020/10/20/US-West-Coast-2020/"/>
    <id>http://j.yud.co.za/stories/2020/10/20/US-West-Coast-2020/</id>
    <published>2020-10-21T01:23:30.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-11-10T03:49:44.517Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;In ~Aug 2019 I made plans to fly down to South Africa to hike the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hikingsouthafrica.co.za/the-otter-trail/&quot;&gt;Otter Trail&lt;/a&gt;. Due to circumstances out of my control I was forced to change my plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the pandemic in full swing I requested ~4 weeks of leave so that I could quarantine in SA before the hike… but that was early on and optimistic. When it became clear I would have to cancel I planned this roadtrip (using three of the four weeks) instead.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
